ef.edu 2019-05-26

# Privacy Policy

### 1\. Your consent

By submitting your personal data to www.ef.edu (hereinafter EF.edu) you automatically accept that EF International Language Schools B.V. or any other corporate entity in the EF Group ( **"EF"** ) registers and stores said personal data for the specific purposes outlined below in this Privacy Policy. You also agree to that your personal data may be transferred to and stored in a country that is not a member of the European Union or part of the European Economic Area. Please note that the reference to EF in this Privacy Policy covers all entities within the EF group of companies.

### 2\. Information about you

When you make a reservation for a course or request brochures on our site, we will need to collect certain information about you such as your name, address, email address, sex, phone number and date of birth. We do not share personal information about you with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your reservation. 

The personal information you provide when making a reservation or placing an order for brochures is only used to complete that reservation or order. We will not use such information in order to send updates, brochures on our new products and services or other marketing material to you, unless you have explicitly indicated this in the request form you have completed.

When answering emails, we will use return email addresses. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

### 3\. Information about a friend

If you wish to send a digital postcard or tell a friend about a particular program, we will ask for the recipient’s name, email address and phone number. The information provided will only be used to confirm message delivery and it will not be shared with outside parties except to the extent necessary to confirm that message. 

The information you provide to create a message is only used for that purpose and it is only disclosed to the recipient.

### 4\. Information about all visitors of ef.edu

EF may gather certain usage information from EF.edu, like the numbers and frequency of visitors to our web site. Such information may be provided to reputable third-party vendors. The data is only used on the aggregate and does not include any personally identifying information.

### 5\. Children's privacy

For the protection of children’s privacy, we require parental consent from users under the age of 16 who wish to make a reservation for a course. 

### 6\. Use of cookies

EF uses a technology nicknamed "cookies". Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. They tell us how and when pages on our site are visited and by how many people.

Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, although they do identify a user’s computer. We do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information in order to detect who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent this. If you do so however, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site. The complete online reservation process can for example only be accessed if you accept cookies.

### 7\. Accuracy

EF will at your request or on our own initiative replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, accurate or outdated personal data on you.

### 8\. Data security

Personal information collected by EF.edu is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public.

### 9\. Areas not covered by this private policy

Personal information that you provide through chat sessions or email exchanges are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We will protect your privacy to the best of our ability by monitoring the sessions, but please keep in mind that you control the information you disclose when you are in a public forum. You should always be careful when distributing your personal information in this manner.

Moreover, it is important to be aware of that this policy only applies to EF.edu and not to other companies’ or organizations’ web sites to which we may link.

### 10\. Amendments

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post any amendments on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it to other companies.

### 11\. Your opinion

If you have any questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by clicking here.
